comparetv.com.au 2019-09-12

# CompareTV Australia Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions

TWENTY/TWENTY DIGITAL PTY LTD, a company registered in Australia with business number 20 166 855 401 whose registered address is at Suite C, 13/1 Vuko Place, Warriewood NSW 2102.  (“CompareTV”, “We” or “Us”) takes your privacy very seriously. We want to assure you that your information and data is safe with Us. We employ highest standard of physical and electronic measures to protect the safety, security and secrecy of your personal information.

We recommend you read this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when CompareTV, acting as data controller, collects personal information about you and how CompareTV will use your personal data.

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the persons that use the website [www.comparetv.com.au](http://www.comparetv.com.au/) (the “Website”) and CompareTV service (the “Service”) according to the Terms of Service through the Website on any device (the “Device”), such as, but with no limitation to, a desktop computer, laptop computer, tablet, mobile phone or any other consumer electronic device.

We would like You to know that We do not sell your information to anyone whatsoever. We ensure complete secrecy and privacy of your data entrusted to Us. We also enter into confidential and processing data agreements with employees and suppliers among others to protect the confidentiality of your information.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to information We collect about the users of the Website (”You“ or User(s)”), as further defined in our Terms of Service [www.comparetv.com.au/terms](http://www.comparetv.com.au/terms).

## Your consent

By using the Service, visiting the Website and/or submitting your personal information You consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

## What information We may collect and hold about You

You hereby consent and authorise CompareTV to use your personal information for the provision of the Service, as defined herein and in the Terms of Service, as well as in order to disclose the relevant personal information in accordance with the Privacy Policy.

In order to be able to use the Service, You do not need to register but we are building an email database for newsletters. Should you wish to sign up for such newsletter We will ask for your first and last name as well as your email address.

While using the Service We automatically record information from your Device and its software as well as your activity using the Service, including, but with no limitation to, your Device Internet Protocol address (the “IP address”), browser type, the web page visited before You were redirected or came to our website, information you search for on our website, identification numbers associated with Your Device(s), browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation, Your locale preferences, system configuration information, your mobile carrier, other interactions with the Service, and other data recorded by Google Analytics that You can [read more about here.](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)

## Why and how We collect and use the information about You

We gather the information about You through the Website. We may use your personal information to:

a)     administer the Website and business;

b)     personalise the website for You;

c)     enable your use of the Services available on the Website;

d)     optimise user experience;

e)     optimise Our content;

f)      track conversions on other sites from Our site visitors;

g)     send you non-marketing commercial communications;

h)     send you marketing communications relating to Our businesses further specified in this Privacy Policy;

i)      provide third parties, such as Our media partners with statistical and traffic information about the Users of the Website (those third parties will not be able to identify any individual User from that information);

j)      deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Website and the Service;

k)     keep the Website secure and prevent fraud;

l)      verify compliance with the Terms of Service governing the use of the Website; and

CompareTV will use contractual or other means to provide a comparable level of protection while the information is being processed by a third party.

## How we protect Your information

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, theft, unauthorised access, destruction or alteration of your personal information and non-personal information. We will store all the personal information You provide on our secure (password-protected) servers located in Australia.

We have put in place security procedures as well as technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal information. When You enter personal information, We encrypt the transmission of that Information using socket layer technology (SSL). It is your responsibility to use a browser that is SSL-enabled, such as Chrome, Firefox, Safari or Internet Explorer when your personal information is transmitted over the Internet.

We use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information. However, You should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason We cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from You or to You via the Internet.

## Disclosure

We will disclose Information about You only when the disclosure is required or authorised by law or by this Privacy Policy.

## Marketing

We  may also wish to provide You with information about special features of the Website or any other service or products We think may be of interest to You. If You would rather not receive this information, You can opt-out by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’link contained in the email communication. If You agree to Us providing you with this type of information, You can always opt out at a later date.

We may also want to provide You with related information from third parties We think may be of interest to You. If You would rather not receive this information, You can opt out by by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’link contained in the email communication. If You agree to Us providing you with third party marketing information, You can always opt out at a later date.

## Access to Your information and updating and correcting Your information

You may exercise your rights of access, request of correction, erasure and objection of your personal information or revoke your consent for receipt of commercial communications by sending such request to: [editor@comparetv.com.au](mailto:operations@comparetv.com.au).

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to CompareTV changes, for example if you change your email address or name or if you wish to cancel your  newsletter subscription and delete your personal information from the Website, please let Us know by sending an e-mail to [editor@comparetv.com.au](mailto:operations@comparetv.com.au)  You may ask Us, or We may ask you, to correct information You or We think is inaccurate, and You may also ask Us to remove information which is inaccurate.

## Overseas transfers

We will not purposely transfer your information overseas but You need to bear in mind that due to the global nature of the Internet the information you provide may be transferred to countries that do not have similar protections in place reading your data and restrictions on its use. We take steps to make sure adequate protections are in place to ensure the security of your information. By submitting your Information You consent to the above described transfers.

## Complaints handling

If You have any complaints regarding this policy or related to privacy, please forward them to [editor@comparetv.com.au](mailto:operations@comparetv.com.au).

## Sale of business

If CompareTV’s business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We keep the Privacy Policy under regular review. If We change the Privacy Policy We will post the changes on the Website, and place notices on other pages of the Website, so that You may be aware of the information We collect and how We use it at all times. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 5 July, 2018.

## How to contact CompareTV

We welcome your views about the Website and the Privacy Policy. If You would like to contact Us with any queries or comments please send an email to: [editor@comparetv.com.au](mailto:operations@comparetv.com.au).
